<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nng on Staysail Systems</title>
    <link>http://staysail.tech/tags/nng/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nng on Staysail Systems</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>info@staysail.tech (Staysail Systems, Inc.)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@staysail.tech (Staysail Systems, Inc.)</webMaster>
    
	<atom:link href="http://staysail.tech/tags/nng/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://staysail.tech/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@staysail.tech (Staysail Systems, Inc.)</author>
      <guid>http://staysail.tech/books/</guid>
      <description>Books We Have Published In addition to offering custom development and consulting services, we at Staysail Systems have authored the following books, helping us to share our expertise with you.
       NNG Reference Manual
Written by Garrett D&amp;#8217;Amore This manual is the authoritative and official reference for the NNG project, encompassing the entire set of manual pages produced for the project. For more information, including purchasing and availability, please see the homepage for the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NNG Reference Manual</title>
      <link>http://staysail.tech/books/nng_reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@staysail.tech (Staysail Systems, Inc.)</author>
      <guid>http://staysail.tech/books/nng_reference/</guid>
      <description>Written by Garrett D&amp;#8217;Amore This manual is the authoritative and official reference for the NNG project, encompassing the entire set of manual pages produced for the project.
   Availability While the content is available as part of the NNG project, you can also purchase a paperback desk edition, or electronic book formats compatible with all popular e-readers.
 If you plan to buy an eBook version, please consider purchasing from Leanpub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NNG Reference Manual (Errata)</title>
      <link>http://staysail.tech/books/nng_reference/errata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>info@staysail.tech (Staysail Systems, Inc.)</author>
      <guid>http://staysail.tech/books/nng_reference/errata/</guid>
      <description>Errata This page lists errata for books that we have published.
 NNG Reference Manual (First Edition, May 2018) Only issues found with the books are reported here. The NNG manual pages located on the NNG are tracked and updated using the NNG GitHub Issues page.
  The description for nng_recv() fails to mention that NNG_FLAG_NONBLOCK may be used for non-blocking operation. The description of nng_recvmsg() does describe this flag, and the description located there can be used in the meantime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>